# Gayan Charith Elgiriya Witharana

+60 1135532399 +94 712506380 Kenwingston Square Garden, Persiaran Bestari, 63000, cyberjaya, Selangor, Malaysia. vgayancharith@gmail.com https://github.com/gayancharith www.linkedin.com/in/gayanwitharan

#### **PROFILE**

Experienced Senior Software Engineer with a Bachelor of Computer Science, currently working at a well reputed company in Malaysia who has more than 6 years of working history in the computer software industry. I am a person with a passion for developing innovative systems that accelerates the efficiency and effectiveness of organizational success.

#### LANGUAGES AND TECHNOLOGIES

- JavaScript, ES6+
- React, React-native, Redux
- PHP, Lumen, Silex, Eloquent
- Node js, Sails js
- GraphQl
- Circleci CI/CD

- Mysql, Couchbase, Mongodb
- .Net Core 2
- HTML and CSS
- Jquery, Vue js
- GitHub, GitLab, Trello and Atlassian Jira

#### **EXPERIENCES**

Archisoft Global Sdn Bhd. (Pvt) Ltd (Feb 2020 - Present)

Senior Front-End Developer

Esshva techq(Pvt) Ltd (Feb 2019 - Jan 2020)

Senior Software Engineer

Thinkcube Systems (Pvt) Ltd (Jan 2017 - Feb 2019)

Senior Software Engineer

Thinkcube Systems (Pvt) Ltd

(Jan 2014 - Jan 2017) Software Engineer Thinkcube Systems (Pvt) Ltd

(Jul 2013 - Jan 2014)

Trainee Software Engineer

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **MTX**

reactjs, netxtjs, redux, react-hooks

A Business to Business application with an admin panel.

Xforce (https://xforce.cornerstonex.com.my/)

reactjs, nextjs, redux, react-hooks

An employee management web application with an admin panel.

#### Madthread - Singapore

Reactjs, Node js, GraphQl, Mongodb, React-native, react hooks, redux, redux-thunk

A subscription base web system and mobile application to facilitate renting and buying clothes.

#### Webestory

Reactjs, react hooks, redux, redux-thunk, draft.js, react ant design

Webestory is an online diary that users can write memories with recordings, videos and share a specific part of the memory with specific friends.

#### Automobile classifieds and cashoffer system - USA

reactjs, redux, redux-thunk, redux-persist, reactive-search, .net core 2 - 2.2 serenity, microservices architecture, rest web-api, react hooks, redux selectors, jest

Classifieds facilitate users to showcase automobiles and receive cashoffer. This also includes inventory and co-part management as well as additional services such as transportation and safe-exchange.

#### eGN Web App

Php, lumen, Vue js, ecmascript-6, couchbase, webpack

Web application that manages citizens data for Sri Lanka government. The application is based on micro service architecture.

<b>Agrinous</b>	Mobile	App	(www.agrinous.com)	

reactjs, react-native, redux, redux-saga, wix-react-native-navigation, ecmascript-6, redux selectors, jest, e2e testing, appium, couchbase-lite

Mobile application for real time processing of livestock sales in Australia. This application handles eid scanning with bluetooth technology to handle stock management, selling and delivery sections.

#### Agrinous Web App (www.agrinous.com)

Php, silex, reactjs, redux, redux-saga, ecmascript-6, couchbase

Web application that manages livestock sales in Australia same as the mobile application.

### Hudlmo Web Portal (www.hudlmo.com)

Node js, Sails js, mongodb, mocha, grunt, javascript, jquery

hudlmo is a collaborative video conferencing web portal with available types of Webinar, Meeting, Huddle and Classes.

#### **Virtual Classroom**

Node js, Web sockets, mongodb, javascript, jquery

A web application that provides the experience of a classroom by providing whiteboard facility, live streaming, public chat, private chat with the lecturer, etc.

#### Leapx

php, zend framework, javascript, jquery, mongodb

Develop an e-Learning system to add courses.

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Computer Science in University of Colombo School of Computing (3.07 GPA) (2010-2013).

## **REFEREES**

References are available on request.